[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What song, performed by Judy Garland in the 1939 movie The Wizard of Oz, won the Academy Award for Best Original Song?", "correct_answer": "Over the Rainbow", "incorrect_answers": ["If I Only Had A Heart", "It Really Was No Miracle", "Love Is a Song"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Red Dawn, when the pilot briefs the Wolverines on the current state of the war, he tells them that in the east they stopped at what geographical landmark?", "correct_answer": "The Mississippi River", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ohio River", "The Missouri River", "The Colorado River"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What deadly and infectious disease that most often attacks the lungs used to be known as consumption?", "correct_answer": "Tuberculosis", "incorrect_answers": ["Measles", "Whooping Cough", "Chicken Pox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eggs have a very high nutrition value. Which of the following substances is not present within an egg?", "correct_answer": "Chlorophyll", "incorrect_answers": ["Phosphorus", "Vitamin D", "Choline"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Barbies full name?", "correct_answer": "Barbara Millicent Roberts", "incorrect_answers": ["Barbie Mary Doe", "Barbie Madonna Smith", "Barbara Monroe Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to an indicator when touched by an acid or a base?", "correct_answer": "the color changes", "incorrect_answers": ["it vibrates", "it dissolves", "it corrodes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 2004 movie National Treasure, what was hidden behind the brick at the clock tower?", "correct_answer": "Ben Franklins unique glasses", "incorrect_answers": ["A piece of the Liberty Bell", "The pipe of magic", "A can of coins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Grizzly bears are strict carnivores.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I shot up an entire police station full of cops just to kill one woman for something she might have done in the future. Who am I?", "correct_answer": "The Terminator", "incorrect_answers": ["Rambo", "John Mcclane", "Indiana Jones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturn is the furthermost planet that can be seen with the naked eye.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements is true about the turtle-dove?", "correct_answer": "They are viewed as a symbol of love.", "incorrect_answers": ["They are not related to the pigeon.", "They have never been domesticated.", "They are flightless"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress portrayed Miss Celie in the movie The Color Purple?", "correct_answer": "Whoopi Goldberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Halle Berry", "Oprah Winfrey", "Ester Rolle"]}]